This is bad.
It's already been two minutes.
I can't wait any longer!
Sophia, Thunder Arm!
Roger.
If I send a weak electric
shock current through the swamp,
it should get him out of the water.
But the problem is
Keisuke's father.
He looked pretty weak already...
Can his body withstand the current?
What should I do?
Is this decision...
...really the right one?!
She's stubborn.
Just give up and leave,
you dumb chicken!
There's no time to hesitate!
If I do nothing,
he'll die for sure!
I'll roll the dice!
Now!
All right!
Not good, he's not breathing!
Don't you die on me!
Please, Keisuke's father!
Don't die!
Keisuke's waiting for you!
Please! Come back!
Please! Keisuke's father! Please!
I knew Brother possessed
the Righteous Egg.
The destructive force behind
his attacks...
I knew it had to be the Egg.
Does that mean
this is a Second Awakening?
But it's so different from
when it happened to me...
That deep red aura...
I sense a powerful darkness in it.
Big Brother...
Don't use
the Righteous Egg's power!
I'm afraid once you do...
you'll be changed forever!
Now that's a good child.
This is what I've been waiting for...
The Awakening of Ruin.
Now, show me...
the evil power that lies within.
I have to say,
you seem different than earlier.
But you're still just
a Goshikidori.
Awakened or not, you're still weak
and still no match for me.
What do you think you can do to me
in my current state?
You still can't lay a single finger on—
I couldn't see that!
A-Are you kidding me?!
A puny chicken?
Don't you dare...
underestimate me!
Don't mess with me!
There's no way I could lose to you,
a lowly Goshikidori!
Die, die, die, die,
die, die, die, die!
We have to destroy
that sphere in his chest!
Hatsu!
Bou! Ten!
Ultra...
Explosive...
Chicken Leg!
Shatter!!
Damn!
It's too hard!
Bastards...
I'm gonna turn you into
ground chicken!
Take this!
Die!!
Super...
Kokekokko!
I was chosen!
I can't lose to the likes of you!
No matter what!
I won't lose!
W-What?!
That sphere isn't breaking!
It's regenerating his body parts
before they're destroyed?!
Damn,
his life force is off the charts!
Not good!
He's losing power!
Damn it, is he at his limit?
No, that's not it!
He's focusing all of his power
on one spot.
He's putting everything into the
sphere!
It's over, Father.
EPISODE 12: WHAT THE BIRDS, BEASTS,
AND TREES SHARE
Are you okay, Brother?
What, this? It's nothing.
That incredible energy...
It was so dark and overwhelming.
Once a Righteous Egg is awakened,
there's no going back.
That awakening might
have been forbidden.
It's possible that
he could lose his sanity,
and his heart and mind might
get swallowed up in darkness...
I won't let that happen!
Mister!
I missed you!!
Huh? You're badly hurt!
Are you okay, Mister?
Y-Yeah...
Oh, good!
Guess what!
I don't remember it too well,
but I defeated the monster
inside of Morio's head!
I gave it my all!
Why aren't you praising me?
By the way, where is Morio?
Piyoko...
Morio's... dead.
What...?
You're lying...
That's impossible!
Morio...
But we just saved you!
Why did you die?!
No, Morio!!
You can't die!
Please come back!
Morio––!!
- I'm...
- Mori—!
...alive
Morio's a zombie!!!
Morio?!
Ow!
Ow, ow, ow...
Oh!
I'm... alive!
I'm...
...alive!!
M-Morio, is that really you?
Oh, Keiji!!
I don't really get it,
but I just tried really hard
to stay alive...
and I didn't die!
I think my life force is
just pretty darn tough!
You're so crazy, damn it...
You're so amazing, Morio!
You're so amazing!
Mo-ri-o! Mo-ri-o!
M-M-Miss Elizabeth!
H-How's Father––?!
He's fine.
He's alive.
I think he'll regain
consciousness soon.
T-Thank you so much,
Miss Elizabeth!
P-Please let me carry him.
Father...
We really won...
Y-Yes...
To think that his awakening
could make him so powerful...
For now, I'll keep my Brother's
awakening a secret...
Excuse me...
With all this commotion, I believe
the police will be on their way.
We should get out of here soon.
Good point.
Let's hurry!
Y-Yes!
Brother?
Stubborn bastard!
- This time around, I'll stop–!
- Brother, wait!
Something's weird...
I don't sense any murderous intent
from him.
Hikari...
Hikari!
My precious Hikari...
My precious treasure.
I'm home!
Welcome back!
What are you doing?
Sorting through this album.
Wow, I haven't seen these before.
There's multiples of the same pose...
You were so cute I always had
to pull you close for pictures.
That must be why I was
wiggling away in half of them.
Back then, I was so anxious
being a single mom.
Everyone disapproved,
but you grew up so well.
I'm so grateful.
Not having a father
must have been tough...
I'm so sorry.
I-It's fine!
I had you!
Oh, look at the time!
I'm gonna be late to
my cleaning job!
I'm sorry, Hikari!
Dinner's on the stove.
Mom, you're going to
wear yourself out.
Can't you just work
afternoon shifts?
I want to make sure
you go to college,
and mature into
a responsible adult.
That's why I'm going to
give it my all,
until I have enough
for your tuition.
Okay. I'll study hard
and make sure you don't have
to work so hard in the future.
Hikari!! You're going to
make me cry!
Stop it! Gross!
Well, I'm headed out!
Okay! See you later!
Yes, this is the Yoshino residence.
This is the Akamori
Police Department.
Kimiko Yoshino was involved in
a car accident and...
What?
Hello? Hello?
Mom...
Mom!
What?
I'm dead...
What's going on?
What's happening to my body?
Where are the Goshikidori?!
Don't come near me!
I can't take it anymore!
Hikari.
It's okay now, Hikari.
M-Mom...
Mom...
You don't need to suffer anymore.
Thank... you...
Did he just say, "Thank you"?
Was he under some
mind control until now?
It's a police helicopter!
Let's hurry!
Morio?
He's still alive.
I don't think he's
a bad guy anymore.
Let's bring him with us.
Are you serious?!
Hold on, Keiji.
Maybe we can learn something
about the Devils.
Let's take him with us.
Do what you want!
What a marvelous battle.
I think your Righteous Egg...
still has some untapped potential.
He will be pleased with this...
Everyone, wake up!
He's come to!
Be careful!
Are you okay?
I-I did such terrible things
to you all...
I'm... truly sorry!
But you were
brainwashed too, right?
Who did this to you?
A woman named Kugone.
W-Who are you?
I knew it.
This child...
is a compatible candidate.
Mom...
It's me...
Hikari...
I'll make you happy, okay?
His love was so powerful,
he became a Demon...
He won't let go of
those thoughts easily.
I won't be able to
control your body...
I'll have to take over
your heart instead.
I'll be your Mama now.
You're not... my mom!
Until you let go of your love
for your mother,
the pain will continue.
We have plenty of time.
The torture lasted over a month.
And then...
How are you feeling today, Hikari?
I feel great, Mama.
My precious Hikari...
There isn't another family
that exists
with a bond as deep as ours...
I know, Mama...
A true bond, right?
I love you, Hikari.
I love you, Mama.
She's too cruel!
She's true evil!
It's unforgiveable!
Kugone must be creating more Devils
all across the country.
All to take over the world?
Yes. And the Goshikidori family
is in the way.
And...
Kugone is most likely after
your Righteous Egg.
My Righteous Egg?
I was told to keep you alive.
I see...
So that was the Righteous Egg,
after all.
Is that Kugone the boss?
Kugone is...
the second-in-command.
Master Gakuma...
That child... Keiji's Awakening
of Ruin has finally occurred.
I see.
Very well, it's almost time then.
Yes, just as you said.
What will you all do now?
I...
completely destroyed that town.
Seems there are still a few Demons
under my control.
So, we're going to help
rebuild the town.
H-Help?
It's true there were no casualties,
but the townspeople are very angry.
But you were brainwashed,
after all...
Still, I need to take
responsibility for what I did.
Whatever happens,
I'll atone for everything.
Huh? Morio's not here!
He said saying goodbye to everyone
was too painful,
so he went off a little bit ago.
Huh?!
You're the worst, Morio!
You didn't give me a chance
to say goodbye to you!
That sounds like him.
Well, I'm sure we'll bump into him
again somewhere.
Next time I see him,
I'm gonna beat him up!
Take care, everyone.
Yes, you too.
Be well!
Bye-bye!
Keiji... Little Chick...
Everyone!
Brother...
It seems like we were after
the same enemy.
Yeah...
So who's this big boss?
He usually stays in his human form.
But when he transforms
into his Demon form...
He's more powerful
than all of you put together.
Where is he now?
I don't know, but...
He did appear out in public once.
There should be footage of him
floating around.
W-What's his name?
The world knows him as...
The White Demon.
That's what they call him.
The White Demon...
It seems our paths
are deeply intertwined...
Wow! It's a great, big pool!!
Wait for me, Sarah.
Even that brat
was able to come back.
Sarah, I promise
I'm gonna get you back!
Kokekokko!
THE END
FAN ART CONTEST AWARDS